Guide to the Steele Ranch Records, 1855-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES A. CORRESPONDENCE: 1855-1973
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 36. 1942, Dec. 30.N.P. Farmers Cooperative Exchange (J.H.H.) to Member., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 1. 1943, Mar. 21.[Ootsa] Lake, B.C Jim Clarke to Will [W.F.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 2. 1943, Mar. 28.Peter Decker to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1943, April 5.Green Oaks Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. C. Mililay to Local Board #282., A.L.S.
    - 4. 1943, April 6.Santa Cruz, Ca. Selective Service System (G.G.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1943, April 8.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (C.W.W.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1943, April 19.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (C.W.W.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1943, May 12.Santa Cruz, Ca. Calif. State Auto. Assc. Inter-Insur. Bur au (C.E.W.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1943, May 18.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to W.F.S. re: Flax Production & Marketing Agreement., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1943, May 25.S.F., Ca. Dr. Harold H. Alverez to C.[B.S.] & W.[F.S.] re: irrigation pipe line., A.L.S.
    - 10. 1943, May 27.S.F., Ca. Dr. Harold H. Alvarez to W.[F.S.] re: irrigation pipe line., A.L.S.
    - 11. 1943, June 3.S.F., Ca. Empire Produce Co. (M.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1943, June 7.Half Moon Bay, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agric., U.S.D.A. War Board (C.H.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1943, June 17.S.F., Ca. Balfour, Guthrie & Co., Ltd. to Federal Land Bank., T.L.
    - 14. 1943, June 19.N.P. Cornell Tractor Co. to [W.F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1943, June 26.Heart Mountain, Wyoming. May Kita to Mrs. Steele [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 16. 1943, July 21.San Jose, Ca. Anglo-Calif. Nat'l. Bank (W.S.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1943, Aug. 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1943, Sept. 28.N.P. May Kita to Mrs. Steele [C.B.S.] re: crops., A.L.S.
    - 19. 1943, Oct. 4.Half Moon Bay, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agric. U.S.D.A. War Board (C.H.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1943, Oct. 14.Camp Cooke, Ca. Capt. Francis Ayres to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1943, Oct. 25.Santa Cruz, Ca. Coast Counties Gas & Electric Co. (L.C.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1943, Dec. 3.Denver, Colorado. Denver Dry Goods Co. (F.E.N.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1943, Dec. 10.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley. (W.D.E.) to Fed. Land Bank Borrowers., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1943, Dec. 27.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Boothe Fruit Co. re: price of cabbage seed., T.L.
    - 25. 1943, Dec. 27.Same as # 24.
    - 26. 1943, Dec. 27.S.F., Ca. Dorothy H. Huggins to Mrs. Steele [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1943, Dec. 29.N.P. Farmers Coop. Exchange (J.H.H.) to Member., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 1. 1944, Jan. 24.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Fed. Land Bank., T.L.
    - 2. 1944, Jan. 27.San Jose, Ca. Anglo-Calif. Nat'l. Bank (W.S.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1944, Jan. 28.Berkeley, Ca. Fed. Land Bank of Berkeley (C.P.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1944, Feb. 9.San Jose, Ca. Anglo-Calif. Nat'l. Bank (W.S.K.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1944, Feb. 10.S.F., Ca. Prudential Insurance Co. of America (F.R.) to J.J. Johnson., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1944, Feb. 19.Santa Cruz, Ca. Johnson & Andersen to Anglo-Calif. Nat'l. Bank., T.L.
    - 7. 1944, Mar. 15.San Jose, Ca. Barbe Tractor & Equipment Co. (G.B.) to W.S.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1944, April 21.San Jose, Ca. San Jose Production Credit Assc. (R.H.H.*) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1944, May 11.Same as # 8.
    - 10. 1944, May 12.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.] to San Jose Credit Corp., T.L.
    - 11. 1944, May 12.Same as # 10.
    - 12. 1944, July 20.San Jose, Ca. Mechanical Farm-Equipment Distributors. (J.R.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1944, July 25.S.F., Ca. Fairbanks, Morse & Co. (W.H.M.) to W.F.S. re: platform scales., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1944, July 26.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.] to Fairbanks, Morse & Co., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1944, July 26.San Jose, Ca. Mechanical Farm-Equipment Distributors (J.R.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1944, Aug. 10.San Jose, Ca. Mech. Farm-Equip. Distributors (J.R.D.) to W.F.S., T.L.
    - 17. 1944, Sept. 5.S.F., Ca. C.S. Malilay to Mr. & Mrs. W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1944, Sept. 20.Berkeley, Ca. Pacific Guano Co. (J.B.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1944, Sept. 26.Des Moines, Iowa. May Kita to Mrs. Steele [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1944, Sept. 29.New York, N.Y. Herbert Hoover to Hulda [Mrs. Charles McLean]., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1944, Oct. 1.N.P. Farmers Cooperative Exchange, Inc. (J.H.H.) to Members., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1944, Oct. 9.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.] to Local Board No. 55., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1944, Nov. 28.S.F., Ca. Fireman's Fund Indemnity Co. to Our Insureds., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1944, Dec. 20.S.F., Ca. Prudential Insur. Co. of America to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1945, Jan. 2.S.F., Ca. New York Life Insur. Co. (P.L.H.) to C.M.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1945, Jan. 10.S.F., Ca. C. Malilay to Mr. & Mrs. W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 27. 1945, Jan. 26.New York, N.Y. New York Life Insur. Co. (F.B.) to C.M.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1945, Feb. 25.Des Moine Iowa. Equitable Life Insur. (A.T.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1945, Mar. 17.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to State Fish & Game Commission re: Waddell Lagoon., T.L.
    - 30. 1945, Mar. 27.Same as #29.
    - 31. 1945, Mar. 28.Santa Cruz, Ca. Stanford G. Smith to Mr. & Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1945, April 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Farmers Coop. Exchange, Inc. (J.H.H.) to Member., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1945, April 10.Emeryville, Ca. Air Reduction Sales Co. (H.W.S.) to Green Oak Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1945, April 17.S.F., Ca. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. (W.J.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1945, May 15.Philippines. Philip Patterson Capt. TC to Will [W.F.S.] & Katherine [C.B.S.] Steele., tel.
    - 36. 1945, May 23.S.F., Ca. Sons of the American Revolution (H.G.M.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1945, July 2.Santa Cruz, Ca. Farmers Cooperative Exchange (J.H.H.) to Member re: Senate Bill # 615 and definition of Agricultural Labor., T.L.S.
    - 38. 1945, July 6.S.F., Ca. Calif. Society of the Sons of the American Revolution (H.G.M.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1945, July 6.S.F., Ca. Calif. Soc. of the Sons of the American Revolution (D.S.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1945, Oct. 16.S.F., Ca. Calif. Soc. of the Sons of the American Revolution (H.G.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 41. 1945, Nov. 29.Half Moon Bay. U.S. Dept. of Agric. (J.J.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 1. 1946, Jan. 31.S.F., Ca. Pacific Pipe Co. (E.I.G.) to S.F.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1946, Feb. 5.S.F., Ca. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. (W.J.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1946, Feb. 19.Lezo Capiz, P.I. Conrado Malilay to Mr. & Mrs. W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 4. 1946, Feb. 25.S.F., Ca. Pacific Pipe Co. (E.I.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1946, Mar. 5.S.F., Ca. Pacific Pipe Co. (E.I.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1946, Mar. 21.Burlingame, Ca. American Red Cross (L.O.W.) to Mrs. F.G. Williamson., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1946, April 16.Santa Cruz, Ca. Farmers Coop. Exchange, Inc. (J.H.H.) to Member., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1946, May 13.Stillwater, Okla. S. [Muneno] to Walter., A.L.S.
    - 9. 1946, May 22.Oakland, Ca. Montgomery Ward [Dept. store] to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1946, May 31.Seaside, Ca. Ed Mckinsey to W.[F.]S. re: permit to haul lumber through State Park land., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1946, June 26.Hollister, Ca. Division of Fish & Game (J.P.V.) to [W.F.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 12. 1946, July 9.Oakland, Ca. D. [Spinaer] to Mrs. Steele [C.B.S.]., P.C.S.
    - 13. 1946, July 9.Green Oak Ranch, Davenport, Ca. Unknown to George N. Cook., T.L.
    - 14. 1946, July 15.N.P. Theodore J. Hoover to W.[F.]S., T.L.
    - 15. 1946, July 18.Green Oak Ranch, Davenport, Ca. C.[B.]S. to Senator Ray Judah. (Letter torn)., T.L.
    - 16. 1946, July 18.N.P. C.[B.]S. to Senator Ray Judah., A.L.S.
    - 17. 1946, July 26.Santa Cruz, Ca. Senator H.R. Judah to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1946, Aug. 5.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.E.S. to Senator H.R. Judah re: damaged irrigation pipe line., T.L.
    - 19. 1946, Aug. 5.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. W.F.S. to Senator H.R. Judah re: damaged irrigation pipe line. (letter wrinkled)., T.L.
    - 20. 1946, Sept. 16.Des Moine, Iowa. Equitable Life Insur. Co. (M.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1946, Sept. 27.Green Oak Ranch, Davenport, Ca. Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.] to Senator R.H.[H.R.] Judah re: damaged irrigation pipe line., T.L.
    - 22. 1946, Sept. 27.Green Oak Ranch, Davenport, Ca. W.F.S. to Senator H.R. Judah re: damaged irrigation pipe line., T.L.
    - 23. 1946, Oct. 8.Half Moon Bay, Ca. Dante Dianda to Bill [W.F.S.] re: damaged irrigation pipe line., A.L.S.
    - 24. 1946, Oct. 8.N.P. Senator H.R. Judah to W.F.S. re: damaged irrigation pipe line., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1946, Oct. 21.Watsonville, Ca. Farmers Coop. Exchange, Inc. (C.E.P.) to Mr. & Mrs. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 26. 1946, Oct. 21.Sacramento, Ca. Dept. of Public Health (E.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 27. Same as # 26.
    - 28. 1946, Oct. 25.N.P. Unknown to Kate [C.B.S.]., T.L.
    - 29. 1946, Dec. 10.S.F., Ca. Firemans Fund Indemnity Co. to Our Insureds., T.L.
    - 30. 1946, Dec. 24.S.F., Ca. Paul Elder & Co. (M.R.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1946, Dec. 29.Oakland, Ca. Stokely Foods Inc. (J.H.B.) to F.W.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 1. 1947, Jan. 2.Half Moon Bay, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agric. (J.J.M.) to W.F.S. re: fertilization of flax., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1947, Jan. 8.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (B.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1947, Feb. 27.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to Flax Growers re: price of flax., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1947, Mar. 4.Aptos, Ca. Santa Cruz County Farm Bureau (E.C.B.) to Calif. Farm Bureau Fed., T.L.
    - 5. 1947, Mar. 7.Redwood City, Ca. Wayne R. Millington to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1947, Mar. 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Stanford G. Smith to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1947, Mar. 10.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (I.H.P.) to E.C. Brownlee., T.L.
    - 8. 1947, April 15.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to Flax Growers re: flax prices., T.L.
    - 9. 1947, May 8.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (C.A.R.) to W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1947, May 8.Green Oak Ranch, Davenport, Ca. W.F.S. to Charles A. Rummel re: damaged irrigation pipe line., T.L.
    - 11. 1947, May 13.N.P. Senator H.R. Judah to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.] re: damaged irrigation pipe line., T.L.
    - 12. 1947, May 13.Same as # 11.
    - 13. 1947, May 16.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (C.A.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1947, May 20.Santa Cruz, Ca. Stanford G. Smith to Mr. & Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1947, May 20.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (C.A.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1947, May 31.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. C.[B.]S. to Norwood Smith re: pipe line right-of-way., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1947, June 2.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to Flax Growers re: flax prices., T.L.
    - 18. 1947, June 18.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to Flax Growers re: flax crops., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1947, June 18.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T. to [W.F.] Steele., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1947, June 25.Palo Alto, Ca. University Realty Co. (N.B.s.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1947, June 28.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. C.[B.]S. to Norwood Smith., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1947, July 14.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. to J.J. McNamara., T.L.
    - 23. 1947, July 14.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. C.B.S. to Charles A. Rummel re: damaged irrigation pipe line., A.L.S.
    - 24. 1947, July 14.N.P. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (C.A.R.) to J.J. McNamara., T.L.
    - 25. 1947, July 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. Insur. Co. of North America to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1947, July 23.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (A.E.O.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1947, Aug. 12.Redwood City, Ca. Ella [S. Allen] to Catherine [C.B.S.]., P.C.S.
    - 28. 1947, Aug. 14.Half Moon Bay, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agric. (J.J.M.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S. re: oat straw prices & cost of baling., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1947, Sept. 1.Santa Cruz, Ca. Farmers Cooperative Exchange (J.H.H.) to Member re: feeds - corn, barley, wheat., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1947, Sept. 11.Redwood City, Ca. Garden City Products Co. (E.S.A.) to C.[B.]S. re: weight of wheat., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1947, Oct. 2.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to Flax Growers re: flax prices., T.L.
    - 32. 1947, Oct. 8.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to Flax Growers re: flax prices., T.L.
    - 33. 1947, Oct. 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Stanford G. Smith to Mr. & Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1947, Oct. 13.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1947, Oct. 15.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to Flax Growers re: flax prices., T.L.
    - 36. 1947, Oct. 17.Same as # 35.
    - 37. 1947, Oct. 17.Same as # 35.
    - 38. 1947, Oct. 29.Emeryville, Ca. Air Reduction Sales Co. (H.W.S.) to Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1947, Oct. 31.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1947, Nov. 6.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to W.F.S. re: flax prices., T.L.S.
    - 41. 1947, Nov. 10.S.F., Ca. Firemans Fund Indemnity Co. to Our Insureds., T.L.
    - 42. 1947, Nov. 14.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (A.E.O.) to W.W.S., T.L.S.
    - 43. 1947, Nov. 17.S.F., Ca. Associated Indemnity Corp. (B.G.) to Member., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1947, Nov. 19.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (A.E.O.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 45. 1947, Dec. 8.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (B.G.) to W.W.S., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1947, Dec. 17.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T. to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.
    - 47. 1947, Dec. 18.Santa Cruz, Ca. Stanford G. Smith to Edward F. Treadwell., T.L.
    - 48. 1947, Dec. 24.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (A.E.O.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 1. 1948, Feb. 2.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.
    - 2. 1948, Feb. 4.Same as # 1.
    - 3. 1948, Feb. 6.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1948, Feb. 7.S.F., Ca. Treadwlll & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.
    - 5. 1948, Feb. 9.Same as # 4.
    - 6. 1948, Mar. 10.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (B.G.) to Member., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1948, Mar. 25.Long Beach, Ca. J.V. Harbaugh to W.F.S., tel.
    - 8. 1948, Mar. 25.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1948, Mar. 27.San Jose, Ca. Pacific Gas & Electric Co. (T.W.S.) to Agricultural Customers., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1948, April 2.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.
    - 11. 1948, April 2.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.H. Augustus., T.L.
    - 12. 1948, April 23.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to Flax Growers., T.L.
    - 13. 1948, May 6.Santa Cruz, Ca. Calif. State Auto. Assc. (C.E.W.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1948, May 7.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.
    - 15. 1948, May 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Stanford G. Smith to Edward F. Treadwell., T.L.
    - 16. 1948, May 11.Same as # 13.
    - 17. 1948, May 17.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1948, May 21.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1948, May 25.S.F., Ca. Same as # 18.
    - 20. 1948, May 20.Oakland, Ca. The Oliver Corp. (J.H.B.) to W.[F.]S. re: farm equipment., A.L.S.
    - 21. 1948, May 27.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (S.F.T.) to D.G. Goldman., T.L.
    - 22. 1948, May 27.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1948, June 1.Oakland, Ca. Oliver Corp. (J.H.B.) to [W.F.]S. re: farm equipment., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1948, June 2.S.F., Ca. Pacific Pipe Co. (E.I.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1948, June 2.Berkeley, Ca. Armco Drainage & Metal Products, Inc. (W.T.J.) to W.F.S. re: steel pipe - prices., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1948, June 6.San Jose, Ca. H.C. Darling to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1948, June 7.S.F., Ca. Montague Pipe & Steel Co. (W.J.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1948, June 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Stanford G. Smith to Mr. & Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1948, June 10.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.
    - 30. 1948, June 11.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1948, June 18.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (E.M.*) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1948, June 22.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Stanford G. Smith re: pipe line right-of-way., T.L.
    - 33. Same as # 32.
    - 34. 1948, June 24.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.
    - 35. 1948, July 6.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.
    - 36. 1948, July 8.N.P. Unknown to William Cress, M.D. re: health insurance., T.L.
    - 37. 1948, July 8.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (E.M.*) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 38. 1948, July 12.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.
    - 39. 1948, July 14.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to Stanford G. Smith., T.L.
    - 40. 1948, July 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Johnson & Anderson Insur. to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 41. 1948, July 23.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to Flax Growers., T.L.
    - 42. 1948, Aug. 23.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 43. 1948, Aug. 23.Same as # 42.
    - 44. 1948, Aug. 23.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 45. 1948, Sept. 23.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to W.F.S. re: flax prices., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1948, Sept. 28.S.F., Ca. El Dorado Oil Works (H.G.W.) to W.F.S. re: flax crops., T.L.
    - 47. 1948, Oct. 1.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin (E.F.T.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 48. 1948, Oct. 22.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (D.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 49. 1948, Oct. 27.Same as # 48.
    - 50. 1948, Oct. 27.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (D.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 51. 1948, Oct. 28.N.P. Unknown to Treadelll & Laughlin., T.L.
    - 52. 1948, Oct. 25.Santa Cruz, Ca. Farmers Cooperative Exchange, Inc. (W.O.M.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 53. 1948, Nov. 10.S.F., Ca. Firemans Fund Indemnity Co. to Our Insureds., T.L.
    - 54. 1948, Nov. 19.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (B.M.H.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 55. 1948, Nov. 30.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (A.E.O.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 56. 1948, Dec. 2.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (B.G.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 57. 1948, Dec. 9.Santa Cruz, Ca. Farmers Coop. Exchange, Inc. (S.I.R.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 58. 1949, Mar. 2.S.F., Ca. Treadwell & Laughlin to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 59. 1949, Mar. 9.S.F., Ca. Division of Highways (F.A.G.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 60. 1949, April 13.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (B.M.S.) to W.[W.]S., T.L.S.
    - 61. 1949, July 13.Hartford, Conn. Aetna Insur. Co. (E.L.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 62. 1949, July 19.Santa Cruz, Ca. Aetna Insur. Co. to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 63. 1949, Aug. 19.Berkeley, Ca. Farm Bureau Health Program (B.M.S.) to W.W.S., T.L.S.
    - 64. 1949, Sept. 15.Half Moon Bay, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agric. (O.O.) to W.[F.]S. re: flax crons., T.L.S.
    - 65. 1949, Oct. 13.S.F., Ca. Pacific Scientific Co. (H.O.R.) to A.C. Workman., T.L.S.
    - 66. 1949, Oct. 24.Santa Cruz, Ca. Farmers Cooperative Exchange, Inc. (V.R.F.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 67. 1949, Nov. 10.N.P. Roscoe Moss to Vic Herman., tel.
    - 68. 1949, Nov. 10.S.F., Ca. Firemans Fund Indemnity Co. to Our Insureds., T.L.
  - Correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 1. 1950,Washington, D.C. U.S. Treasury Dept. (E.J.M.) to W.F.S. & C.B.S. re: income tax., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1940,Washington, D.C. U.S. Treasury Dept. (E.J.M.) to W.W.S. re: income tax., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1950, April 12.Santa Cruz, Ca. Johnson & Anderson Insur. to W.W.S., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1940, June 2.S.F., Ca. Bank of America (F.E.R.) to W.F.S. & C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1940, June 10.Santa Cruz Ca. Johnson & Andersen Insur. to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1940, Aug. 25.Santa Cruz, Ca. Johnson & Andersen (E.L.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1940, Sept. 12.Santa Cruz, Ca Johnson & Andersen Insur. to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1950, Oct. 11.Same as # 6.
    - 9. 1950, Dec. 4.Santa Cruz, Ca. County 1st. Nat'l. Bank (F.M.) to W.W.S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1951, Sept. 27.Gilroy, Ca. Division of Highways (R.J.N.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1951, Dec. 26.New York, N.Y. Ruberoid Co. to Stockholders., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1952, Jan. 31.S.F., Ca. Transamerica Corp. to Stockholders., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1952, May 3.N.P. Jack Andusus (?) to Unknown., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1952, June 14.Santa Cruz, Ca. Johnson & Andersen (J.J.J.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1952, June 30.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. C.[B.]S. to Herbert Hoover., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1952, July 1.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley Nat'l. Bank (L.H.L.) to Stockholders., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1952, July 23.Santa Cruz, Ca. Johnson & Andersen (L.H.A.) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1952, Aug. 6.[Santa Cruz, Ca.]. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (S.L.T.) to Member., T.L.
    - 19. 1952, Sept. 20.Santa Cruz, Ca. Joslin Brothers (A.J.) to W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1952, Sept. 24.Santa Cruz, Ca. Joslin Brothers (A.J.) to W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 21. 1952, Nov. 10.S.F., Ca. Firemans Fund Group to Our Insureds., T.L.
    - 22. 1952, Nov. 14.S.F., Ca. Johns & Manville Sales Corp. (E.H.) to W.F.S. re: prices - pressure pipe., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1952, Nov. 28.San Mateo, Ca. Jo & Carl [Hoag] to C.[B.S.], W.[F.S.] and W.[W.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 24. 1952, Dec. 10.Half Moon Bay, Ca. R.H. Sciaroni to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1952, Dec. 26.New York, N.Y. Ruberoid Co. to Stockholders., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1953, Mar. 2.Salinas, Ca. Salinas Valley Realty Co. to Mr. Steele., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1953, April 9.S.F., Ca. I. Tabuchi to W.[W.]S., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1953, Aug. 30.S.F., Ca. Louise to C[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1953, Sept. 10.S.F., Ca. Unknown [Louise] to C.[B.S.]., T.L.
    - 30. 1953, Sept. 21.San Jose, Ca. Royal-Liverpool Insur. Group (G.F.N.) to W.W.S., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1953, Sept. 23.S.F., Ca. Unknown [Louise] to C.[B.S.]., T.L.
    - 32. 1953, Oct. 1.S.F., Ca. L. to Unknown [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 33. 1953, Oct. 1.San Jose, Ca. Royal-Liverpool Insur. Group (G.F.N.) to W.W.S., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1953, Oct. 7.S.F., Ca. Louise to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1953, Nov. 13.S.F., Ca. Louise to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 36. 1953, Dec.N.P. Unknown to C.[B.S.]. frag., T.L.
    - 37. 1954, April 8.San Mateo, Ca. Carl [Hoag] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 38. 1954, April 17.Redwood City, Ca. Alan Brown to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.] re: early history of Punta del Año Nuevo - late 1700's to the middle 1800's., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1954, June 10.S.F., Ca. Kelly, Thomas & Kinkead (C.H. to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.], T.L.S.
    - 40. 1954, June 17.S.F., Ca. Kelly, Thomas & Kinkead (C.H.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 41. 1954, Aug. 6.San Jose, Ca. W. Henry Harper, M.D. to Mr. & Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 42. 42. 1954, Oct. 25.Clinton, N.Y. Alan Brown to [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 43. 1954, Nov. 12.Houston, Texas. Daughters of the Republic of Texas (W.D.K.) to [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1955, Jan. 5.San Jose, Ca. Dept. of Agric. - County of Santa Clara (T.[J.]M.) to Friends., A.L.S.
    - 45. 1955, Jan. 22.Chicago, Ill. May (Kita) Mayeda to [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 46. 1955, Feb. 22.Houston, Texas, Sons of the Republic of Texas (J.B.*) to Chapter Member., T.L.S.
    - 47. 1955, Mar. 21.Villa Hidalgo Jal. [T]idencio Garcia to [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.